maurices.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: July 7, 2014**

This Privacy Policy applies to information about you that Maurices Incorporated ("maurices") collects when you use our websites or online features, applications, widgets, or other services including social media services (collectively "Sites"), or interact with us offline. This Policy explains the types of information we may gather from you, how it is handled, with whom it may be shared, and how you may access the data you provide to us.

By visiting our Sites or otherwise interacting with us, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy.

We review and change our privacy practices from time to time. Please review this Privacy Policy each time you interact with us to ensure your continuing familiarity with our current privacy practices. If we make material changes to our policy, we will notify you at the last email address we have in our records for you, or if we do not have an email address for you, at your last known mailing address. Otherwise, all amended terms shall be automatically effective after they are posted here. Your continued interaction with us after such changes have been posted constitutes your agreement to the changes.

**CONTENTS**

**1\. Information We Collect**

We collect personally identifiable information, which is information that identifies a specific individual ("PII"), such as your name, email address, postal address, and telephone numbers. We also collect other information about you, such as demographic information (e.g., your gender, ZIP code, or similar information), information about your preferences and interests, and other information based on the context in which the collection is made, including the information more fully described below. If we combine demographic or similar information with the PII we collect, we will treat the combined information as PII under this Privacy Policy.

The information we collect may be provided by you or by a third party, or may be collected automatically.

**_Information You Provide._** Our practices are described below. You may choose not to provide certain information; however, choosing to do so may prevent you from being able to take advantage of many of our offered features or from conducting transactions.

_Through Your Visits/By Your Request._ We collect the information described above when you use our Sites; contact us to request customer support or otherwise; create an online account; sign up to receive our emails, direct mail, or other advertising; respond to our survey requests; participate in a sweepstakes, contest or promotion; or otherwise communicate with us.

_Through Transactions._ When you make a purchase or otherwise transact with us, whether online or offline, in addition to the information described above, we will retain information regarding those purchases and transactions, such as products purchased, location of purchase, how frequently you buy, features you utilize, offers you redeem, and rewards you earn or redeem.

_Through Social Features, Community Forums, and User Content._ We may provide through our own services or third party services the opportunity for you to post content publicly, such as product reviews, photographs, questions, comments, suggestions, or other content (collectively, "User Content"), or to initiate interactions between our websites or services and third-party websites or services ("Social Features"). Examples of Social Features include enabling you to "like" or "share" content from our websites or services to other websites or services; to login using your username and password for a third-party site or service; or to post information on a third-party platform that references maurices, such as by use of a hashtag.

In addition to providing the information described in previous sections of this policy, by using Social Features, you may also provide maurices with information contained within your social network account, such as your profile information, friend or contacts information, pictures, and interests. Similarly, if you post information on a third-party platform that references a maurices product (e.g., by using a Twitter hashtag associated with maurices in your tweet), your post may be published on or through our Sites, advertising materials, or other publications.

**If you submit User Content or use Social Features, we may publish that information or content online or offline, including in connection with our advertising, marketing, publicity, and promotional activities.**

**_Information Provided by Third Parties._** We may obtain information, including contact information and demographic information, about you from third parties, including our joint marketing partners, the bank that operates our private label credit card program, or other unrelated third parties. We may receive information about you if other users of a third-party website give us access to their profiles and you are one of their "connections" or information about you is otherwise accessible through your "connections" webpage, profile page, or similar page on a social networking or other third-party website or interactive service. We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. In those cases, we will apply this Policy to the combined information.

**_Information We Collect Automatically._** Whenever you browse any of our Sites, maurices and its third-party service providers, including analytics providers and third-party content providers, automatically receive and record certain information, such as your IP address, browser type, type of device you use to access the Sites and domain name from which you arrived at the Site, device identifier, Location-Data (defined below), and specific maurices.com web pages through which you click, among other information ("Usage Information").

To provide location-based services on certain of our Sites, we may need to capture and record certain location-data regarding your use of the Sites and your travels in order to provide location-related functionality ("Location-Data"). We may link that Location-Data to other information that you provide to us or that may be accessed in connection with your use of the Sites.

The methods used to collect Usage Information may include:

_Cookies._ "Cookies" and "Flash cookies" are small files placed on your device to make your shopping experience more efficient, convenient, and personalized. Through the use of these cookies, we and our third-party service providers may automatically collect Usage Information, enable features, or remember your preferences.

Many web browsers allow you to remove or reject cookies. However, these tools may not affect Flash cookie preferences. For more information about disabling Flash cookies, see [www.adobe.com](http://www.adobe.com/). If you choose to disable cookies or Flash cookies, some features of the Sites may not function properly, including the shopping cart and ordering processes.

_Web Beacons._ Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as "1x1 GIFs" or "clear GIFs") may be included in our Sites and in email messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including to count visitors to the Site, to monitor how users navigate the Site, to count how many emails that were sent were actually opened, or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

_Embedded Scripts._ An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device from our server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

**2\. Our Use of Information**

Our primary purpose for collecting PII is for maurices to provide you with a safe, efficient and beneficial experience. To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online and offline about your activities and product interests. We may use information collected from or about you, including your PII and Usage Information:

  * To allow you to participate in the Sites, or features or activities we offer, including sweepstakes, contests, or other prize promotions;
  * To process a transaction or your registration, verify your identity, send you confirmations and receipts, and protect each party from errors, misuse of the Sites, fraud, or any criminal activity;
  * To respond to your inquiries and provide customer service related to your use of the Sites;
  * To verify your eligibility for, and to provide you with, products and services;
  * To contact you regarding any problems with your merchandise order or account;
  * To help us serve you better, enhance, and personalize your shopping experience;
  * To provide you with information about other products and services which may be of interest to you (for information about how to manage these communications, see [Updating My Information and Choices](http://mauricescareteam.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/45#uic);
  * To manage and develop our business and operations, generate statistics and aggregate reports, and for internal business purposes;
  * To meet legal and regulatory requirements;
  * To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for the Sites; and
  * To fulfill any other purpose consistent with this Privacy Policy or for purposes disclosed to you at the time of collection or with your consent.

**3\. Sharing of Information**

We may share information, including PII, about you as follows:

  * With third-party service providers who may assist us in operating the Sites or with marketing or administrative tasks, including creation and distribution of marketing, delivering packages, analyzing data and providing Site analytics, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, powering certain features within a Site, and providing customer service. In those situations, the outside company is performing work for maurices, and maurices takes appropriate steps designed to ensure your privacy and that your PII is used only to provide the services requested by us, and not for other purposes.
  * With Ascena Retail Group, Inc. (the parent company of maurices), other brands owned by Ascena Retail Group, and our business partners for their own marketing (including direct marketing) purposes, unless you opt out as described in [Updating My Information and Choices](http://mauricescareteam.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/45#uic).
  * With third-parties for purposes of sending their own direct marketing messages, unless you opt out as described in [Updating My Information and Choices](http://mauricescareteam.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/45#uic).
  * With third-parties who sponsor or co-sponsor with maurices a sweepstakes, contest, or other prize promotion in which you choose to participate. We also will disclose publicly information about the winner(s) of a prize promotion.
  * When we believe release is appropriate to ensure compliance with the law and the safety and security of our Sites, including in response to legal process and law enforcement requests; to enforce or apply our policies and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, safety or other interests of maurices, our parent company, affiliates and shareholders, or any other organization or individual. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * If maurices goes through a business transition, including a merger, acquisition, sale of all or substantially all of our assets, or any other change in corporate structure, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process.

**4\. Information Collected by Third-Parties**

Information about you may also be collected and stored by third parties, and it remains subject to the third party's privacy practices, including whether the third party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third-party website or service.

**_Analytics Providers and Ad Servers._** We work with vendors (including network advertisers, ad agencies, and analytics companies) to provide us with information regarding traffic on the Site, to serve our advertisements elsewhere online, and to provide us with information regarding the use of the Sites and the effectiveness of our advertisements. For example, if you clicked on one of our advertisements that led you to the Site, our service provider(s) may be able to tell us which advertisement you clicked on and where you were viewing the advertisement.

In connection with serving content and providing analytics and advertisement services, third parties may collect certain information about your visits to the Sites or other websites. These third parties may set and access their own tracking technologies such as those identified [above](http://mauricescareteam.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/45#iwc) and may otherwise collect or have access to your device identifier, Usage Information, and related information about you. We may share device identifier and Usage Information about visitors with third-party advertising companies, analytics providers, and other vendors for similar purposes.

_Tracking Technologies._ Tracking technologies, including those set by third-party network advertisers, may be used to, among other things, target advertisements, prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times and to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you. At this time, we do not respond to browser-based "do not track" signals, but some of the variety of service providers we use to perform advertising and analytics services may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the "opt-out" procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an "opt-out" by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program. Please note opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads while online.

We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with relevant online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, [click here](http://dtmc.maurices.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=61636&cname=Maurices&cmagic=499136&clogo=61636.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). 

**_Social Features and User Content._** If you choose to utilize Social Features or submit User Content, certain information, such as your name, may be displayed in association with that action. If you choose to voluntarily disclose PII, that information will be considered public information and the protections of this Privacy Policy will not apply. We cannot control the use of information disclosed in public forums. You should exercise caution when disclosing information in these public areas and be careful how you disclose your PII.

**_Links to Other Websites and Services._** The Sites may link to third-party websites or content over which we have no control and which are governed by the privacy policies and business practices of those third parties, including the bank that operates our private label credit card program. maurices is not responsible for the privacy practices or business practices of any third party.

**_Prize Promotions._** When you enter a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion, you may be asked to provide registration information such as your name, address, email address and other information, some of which may be optional, in order to participate. That information may be collected by a third party that is sponsoring, or co-sponsoring with maurices, the promotion. If you voluntarily submit PII to enter a sweepstakes on a Site, the information that you submit may be used for sweepstakes administration and prize fulfillment purposes, and it may also be used for future marketing by the Sponsor(s), such as to notify you of a product or promotion that Sponsor(s) think/s may be of interest. Some third parties may use cookies in order to track your progress or number of entries in a promotion. If information is collected and used by a third party in conjunction with a promotion, please review the third party's privacy policy to learn about its privacy practices.

**5\. Promotional Communications**

We may send you emails and/or other promotional information if we have collected your information in any of the ways described above. We will send you text messages only if you sign up to receive text communications. If at any time you do not want to continue to receive information, emails, texts, or mailings, you may change your preferences as described in [Updating My Information and Choices](http://mauricescareteam.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/45#uic).

**6\. How We Protect Personally Identifiable Information**

Whenever maurices handles your PII, we take commercially reasonable steps appropriate to the sensitivity of the information, including by maintaining physical, organizational, and technological safeguards, to protect your information in accordance with this Policy, and to help protect PII against loss or theft and against unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification. Once we receive your transmission, we make commercially reasonable efforts to protect its security on our systems. These safeguards are designed to protect against, but are not a guarantee against, the loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of PII. maurices uses the industry standard encryption protocol known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to encrypt your order information to protect against the decoding of that information by anyone other than maurices. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, warrant or ensure the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us through the Internet, and you do so at your own risk. We retain personal information that we collect only as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or to meet any legal requirements.

**7\. Children**

Our Sites are intended for a general audience and are not intended for use by or targeted to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally information from children under the age of 13. If the parent or guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with PII, the parent or guardian of that child should contact our Customer Service Center (contact details below) and ask to have this PII deleted from our files.

**8\. Consent to Transfer and Storage in the United States**

Your information is stored on servers located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using the Sites, or providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this transfer, processing, and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.

**9\. Updating Information and Choices**

The Sites may contain webpages through which you can correct or update some of the PII you have provided or through which you may be able to unsubscribe or modify the email newsletters or similar communications we send to you. To opt out of PII sharing [click here](http://mauricescareteam.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/56/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xNDkzMzEwMDM0L3NpZC9mVUp4dnlZJTdFVTVkSTZoSHJXUUR4VHdtQm5JS1Y5S21LY0ZoWkplMHRRZjNlTlpJUzZGd2FrM3lsaXhmc3liT0cwTmRTcUZFcllWSl9Lek9VVm93REkwT2NINlF4TkRLV09GUjJVS3VucEVvc0RlRmVUZDRJazVjdyUyMSUyMQ%3D%3D). To opt out of marketing email messages [click here](http://mauricescareteam.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/42/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xNDkzMzEwMDM0L3NpZC9mVUp4dnlZJTdFVTVkSTZoSHJXUUR4VHdtQm5JS1Y5S21LY0ZoWkplMHRRZjNlTlpJUzZGd2FrM3lsaXhmc3liT0cwTmRTcUZFcllWSl9Lek9VVm93REkwT2NINlF4TkRLV09GUjJVS3VucEVvc0RlRmVUZDRJazVjdyUyMSUyMQ%3D%3D). You may also contact us through the information provided below under [Contact Us](http://mauricescareteam.custhelp.com/app/contact/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xNDkzMzEwMDM0L3NpZC9mVUp4dnlZJTdFVTVkSTZoSHJXUUR4VHdtQm5JS1Y5S21LY0ZoWkplMHRRZjNlTlpJUzZGd2FrM3lsaXhmc3liT0cwTmRTcUZFcllWSl9Lek9VVm93REkwT2NINlF4TkRLV09GUjJVS3VucEVvc0RlRmVUZDRJazVjdyUyMSUyMQ%3D%3D). maurices will make requested changes in our active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. Note, however, that information you update or change may persist internally or for maurices' administrative purposes. It is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases, and residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons. Also, if you have made any public postings, these communications generally will not be removed. You can also unsubscribe from marketing emails through the opt-out mechanism included in each marketing email we send to you. Note that we reserve the right to send you certain email or postal communications relating to your use of our Site, service announcements, notices of changes to this Privacy Policy, or similar administrative or transactional messages, and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from marketing communications. If you sign up to receive SMS or MMS messages that may be offered on the Sites, you may unsubscribe by replying "STOP."

**10\. Contact Us**

_By mail:_ maurices Online Customer Service, 105 W Superior St., Duluth, MN 55802

_By email:_ [customerservice@maurices.com](mailto:customerservice@maurices.com)

_By phone:_ 1-866-977-1542

**11\. Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California law, you may request information about how we have shared your information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. You may make the request by either (a) sending a written request via email to [customerservice@maurices.com](mailto:customerservice@maurices.com) and writing "Privacy Policy" in the subject line; or (b) sending a written request via postal mail to: Maurices Online Customer Service, 105 W Superior St., Duluth, MN 55802. In response to your written request, we may provide you with a notice describing the cost-free means to opt-out of our direct marketing promotions and/or other third party information sharing.
